超能量 汽车保安的极品
MagnaVolt. The final word in auto security.
没有尴尬的警报声 不用劳烦警方
No embarrassing alarm noise, no need to trouble the police...
甚至不会耗用你的电池
...and it won't even run down your battery.
超能量
MagnaVolt.
致命的反应
Lethal response.
国际新闻 亚马逊河的核能设施发生排气管爆炸
On the international scene, the Amazon nuclear power facility has blown its stack...
幅射在两林扩散 环保人士认为这是个大灾难
...irradiating the world's largest rain forest. Environmentalists call it a disaster.
不是经常都那样吗
But don't they always?
国内新闻 检察总长马国斯...
In national news, Attorney General Marcos today...
批准在五个城市 发展ED209作战机械人
...approved the ED 209 combat unit for deployment in five American cities...
尽管它的故障被广泛投诉
...despite widespread complaints of malfunction.
卫生局局长已经身亡
The surgeon general is dead.
他在20分钟前被一名好战的"核灵"毒癖者枪杀
Gunned down 20 minutes ago by a militant addict of the deadly designer drug Nuke.
对国内最大的健康威胁...
The greatest health threat facing our nation.
"核灵"
Nuke.
有史以来最易上瘾的毒品
The most addictive narcotic in history.
一个瘟疫...
A plague that...
核灵
Nuke! Nuke!
我们刚接收到以下的片段
This station has just received this transmission from Cain...
是被定罪的谋杀犯和核灵教派领袖勒恩
...convicted murderer and leader of the Nuke cult.
每人都想到天堂
The people want paradise.
（核灵教派领袖）
他们会到的
And they will have it.
这次行刺是勒恩 继上周...
The assassination is the latest act of terrorism by Cain...
炸毁一间戒毒诊所后 最新的恐怖活动
...following the bombing of a drug treatment clinic that left five dead.
谈判失败后 底特律市的警员回到罢工线...
After the latest breakdown in negotiations, Detroit's police returned to the picket line...
向受雇于本市的管理警察部普及消费者产品公司OCP
...demanding better terms from Omni Consumer Products, OCP...
要求更好的待遇
...the corporation contracted by the city to run the police department.
OCP削减我们四成薪金 还取消了我们的退休金
OCP cut our salaries 40 percent and canceled our pensions.
现在甚至拒绝跟我们对话
Now they refuse to even talk to us.
天晓得为什么 他们令我们这么做的
God knows why, but they want this strike.
发生什么事
What happened?
站起来
Get up!
- 捉住他  - 婊子 你弄瞎我的眼了
- Hold him!  - You put my eye out, you bitches!
闭嘴 混蛋
Shut up, you fuckhead!
- 你弄断我的手臂了  - 快点
- You're breaking my fucking arm!  - Hurry!
看这个 他真卑鄙
Look at this. What a nasty man.
今晚收工了 去付钱给老爷和拿我们的东西吧
Night's made. Let's pay Papa and get us what we need.
给我核灵
Nuke me, baby!
- 我会杀死你们两个婊子  - 他起来了 快走
- I'll kill you bitches!  - He's up! Come on!
- 你不懂得用计时器  - 我们走吧
- You're shit with a timer, man!  - Come on! Let's go!
这些东西可以对付一支军队
I'll take out an army with this shit!
我们拿完就走
Let's load up and get the hell out of here!
这支枪的子弹放在哪里
Where's the bullets for this gun, man?
下面第三个抽屉
Third drawer, bottom.
我们该开一辆货车来
We should've brought a truck!
我很喜欢这支枪
I really like this gun, man.
拿完就快走
Just take it and get out.
谢谢你
Thanks.
- 我难以置信  - 什么
- I don't believe this!  - What?
- 有警察  - 警察都在罢工 笨蛋
- It's the cops, man.  - Cops are on strike, stupid.
你听不到吗
Can't you hear that?
- 我告诉你什么了  - 我会对付他
- See. What did I tell you?  - I'll fix him.
你看到吗 我们干掉他了
Did you see that? We got him!
- 厉害 我们走吧  - 不 再来一次
- Beautiful. Come on, man. Let's move it.  - No. One more!
妈的
Nice shit, man.
他妈的警察
Fucking cops!
(瞄准中)
治安警察
Peace officer.
(瞄准中)
你考虑清楚
Think it over, creep.
核灵
Nuke.
不是我的
It's not mine, man.
它在哪里制造
Where is it made?
我说了不是我的 我是清白的
It's not mine, man. I told you! I'm clean!
它在哪里制造的
Where is it made?
我不知道 我只知道在哪里拿得到
I don't know, man! All I know is where I get it!
(首要指令    1:取得公众信任  2:保护无辜者  3:执行法纪)
(有罪案正在发生)
(拘捕状态)
别动
Freeze.
谁也不准动 这是逮捕行动
Nobody move. This is a bust.
女士们 趴下
Ladies, stay down.
来人 打开雪柜
Somebody! Open the fridge, damn it!
快点
Come on!
(禁止瞄准)
混蛋 不可以杀小孩吧
Can't shoot a kid, can you, fucker?
(禁止瞄准)
(重播)
(追踪错误)
不可以杀小孩...
Can't shoot a kid...
(追踪错误)
爸爸 抛回来
Throw it home, Dad!
闭嘴
Shut up!
放下枪 否则他要死 我会一枪轰掉他
Drop it or the little shit's dead! I'll blow its fucking head off, man!
路易斯...
Lewis...
收起它
...hang it up.
(标绘弹道)
你们都不要胡来
Now, no shit from either one of you!
- 也别跟踪我  - 我们不会的
- And don't try to follow me!  - We won't.
这婴孩要跟我走
The baby's going with me!
我会杀了它...
I'll kill it, man. I'll do it. I'll fucking kill it!
我们不可那样做
We can't have that.
(标绘弹道)
好身手呢
Nice shooting.
再见 哲明
See you, Jimmy.
- 妈妈  - 你好
- Hi, Mom.  - Hi.
别那样 停手 停手 雅历
Don't do it! No! Stop... Stop it, Alex!
OCP界认定你为一副...
OCP defines you as a machine...
使用活组织的机器 你要明白这一点
...that utilizes some living tissue. You understand that.
是
Yes.
你是否认为自己是... 人类
And so do you consider yourself human?
我要一个答案
I require an answer.
停止录影
Stop tape.
你可知道你对那女人做了什么
You have any idea what you're doing to that poor woman?
看看她的档案
Take a look at her file.
看吧
Go on.
探员 麦太太... 正在控告OCP
Officer, Mrs. Murphy is bringing suit against OCP.
我叫狄汤姆 我代表她的
My name is Tom Delaney. I'm representing her.
几个月前 她还是不肯离开她的卧房
Up to a few months ago, she wouldn't leave her bedroom.
后来接受了催眠和协调治疗
Then there were hypnotists and harmonic treatments.
然后你就耍花样 每天开车经过她的家
Then you pull this shit! Driving past her house day after day.
监视她 尝试令她以为丈夫仍在世
Spying on her. Trying to make her think her husband is still alive.
她稍为开始接受丧夫之痛
She's barely started to accept the loss.
- 你又来刺激她  - 为什么
- You're ripping her to pieces.  - And for what?
你以为可以再做她丈夫吗
Do you think you could ever be a husband to her?
你可以给她什么
I mean, what can you offer her?
伴侣关系
Companionship?
爱情
Love?
一个男人的爱
A man's love?
不是
No.
继续录影
Roll tape.
你是不是雅历
Are you Alex Murphy?
不是
No.
你是不是人类
Are you human?
不是
No.
你只是一副机器
You are simply a machine.
我是...
I am...
一副机器
...a machine.
只是一副机器
Nothing more.
可以了 停止录影
That'll do it. Stop tape.
你留下来 带她进来
Now, you stay there. All right, go get her.
我们有道德一点吧 给他们一些私隐
Let's be decent about this. Give them some privacy.
没有问题
I don't have a problem with that.
雅历
Alex?
你不认识我
Don't you know me?
你不记得我
Don't you remember me?
他们对你做了什么也不要紧的
Alex, it doesn't matter what they've done to you...
触摸我
Touch me.
是冷的
It's cold.
他们制造了这个...
They made this...
来向我致敬
...to honor him.
- 不 我...  - 你的丈夫死了
- No, I...  - Your husband is dead.
我不认识你
I don't know you.
为何会这样
Why is this happening?
我以为所有通讯系统都是一样
I thought all communication systems were the same.
我想替公司省点钱
I tried to save the company a few bucks.
花了两天才从克利夫兰下载到规格
It took two days to download specs from Cleveland.
我失去了那个客户
I lost the account.
（OCP通讯）
（唯一的选择）
强生 要我来见你真是有损我的尊严
It hardly befits my dignity to have to come to you, Johnson.
市长 抱歉这个轻微的不便之处
Sorry for the slight inconvenience, Your Honor.
繁忙时间里的20分钟不算轻微
Twenty minutes in rush hour isn't slight.
当你是底特律市长时就不算轻微
Not when you're mayor of a major city!
你们何时会发薪给那些警察 让他们恢复执勤
When will you start paying the cops so they'll go back to work?
我们不是慈善机构
We're not a charity.
市政府欠我们三千七百多万元
The city owes us over $37 million.
- 你要宽限我们一点  - 限期就是限期
- You'll have to cut us some slack.  - A deadline's a deadline. Sorry.
我们怎么筹得到那笔钱
How are we supposed to raise that kind of money?
你们不用筹
You aren't.
- 他说什么  - 我们不预期你们付钱
- What the hell is he talking about?  - We don't expect you to pay.
让我给你引述我们的合约
Let me refer you to our contract.
"出现违约情况时..."
"In the event of default...
"OCP将有绝对权利没收所有市内的资产"
...OCP shall have the uncontested right of foreclosure on all city assets."
你签了这个的
You signed this.
我们欠一次付款 你就可以取消赎回权
We miss one payment, and you can foreclose?
我们可以也会实行
We can and we will.
我们要把底特律私有化
We're taking Detroit private.
你故意损害我们的信誉
So you deliberately undermined our credit.
那是容易办的事
That was the easy part.
你们还策划警员罢工
And you engineered the police strike.
你们想底特律陷入困境
You want Detroit to tear itself apart...
让你们可把它像间公司般吞并
...so you can raid it like you would any other corporation!
你们可知道会有多少人命危
Do you know how many people are dying?
- 你们是杀人凶手  - 不要再说
- You're murderers!  - I'd advise you to say nothing further.
这可能会...
It might be...
引致诉讼
...actionable.
胡说
It's bullshit!
- 胡说 你这个老混蛋  - 冷静点
- Bullshit, you senile, old bastard!  - All right, calm down.
- 我们还是走吧  - 我没事
- We better get out of here.  - I'm okay!
- 我们走吧  - 我很冷静
- Calm down. We better leave.  - I'm calm.
- 冷静 放松点  - 我没事
- Calm down. Easy.  - I'm okay.
很好
All right, good.
- 我很自制 没有事  - 一切都好
- I'm in control. Everything is fine. It's okay.  - Relax.
我很好
I'm fine.
各位 还有一件事
One last thing, gentlemen.
我们会控告你们的
We will sue your asses.
尽管做吧
Give it your best shot.
去你的 老头混蛋 简直胡说八道
Fuck you, you old, senile bastard! This is bullshit!
去你的
Fuck you!
- 简直混帐  - 冷静点
- This is bullshit!  - Calm down.
强生 我已很有耐性 五个月了
I've been very patient, Johnson. Five months.
- 她是谁  - 茱莉·费博士
- Who's that?  - That's Dr. Juliette Faxx.
提升了做态度校正组主管
Just moved up to head the Attitude Adjustment team.
五个月 九千万元
Five months. Ninety million dollars!
- 我要看到一些成绩  - 我会给你看看的
- I want to see some results.  - Yes, sir. I'll show you what we have.
OCP领导半机械人研制科技
OCP pioneered cyborg technology.
现在我们跨进了一大步
And now we take a quantum leap forward.
结合软体和有机体系统作操控的
State-of-the-art destructive capabilities...
最新型的攻击装置
...commanded by a unique combination of software and organic systems.
是原装版本的一大改良
In every way, an improvement over the original.
我很荣幸为大家介绍... 机械警察二号
It gives me great pleasure to introduce to you, Robocop 2.
你被拘捕了
You are under arrest.
停止 否则我会开枪
Stop or I'll shoot.
OCP很荣幸介绍 未来的市区保安装备
OCP is proud to present the future of urban pacification:
机械警察二号
Robocop 2.
九千万
Ninety million.
它们都是疯的
They all go crazy.
有情绪问题的机械人
Robots with emotional problems.
不是机械人 是半机械人
No, sir, not robots, cyborgs.
机械装置生物体 我们利用活人组织那是问题所在
Cybernetic organisms. We use living human tissue and that's our whole problem.
被挑选的都是受人尊敬的警察
The candidates were all fine men, respected police officers.
我亲自看过他们的档案
I reviewed their files myself.
老板 警察可能不是我们的最佳人选
Sir, police officers may not be the best candidates for our purposes.
他们只是精壮和雄纠纠的一群
They're a physical bunch. They're macho, body-proud.
除去这部分 他们就变得有自杀倾向
Stripped of all that it's no wonder they become suicidal.
我们唯一成功的是个警察
Our one success was a cop.
对 亚历克斯·墨菲
Well, yes, Mr. Johnson. Alex Murphy.
同辈中的精英 虔诚的爱尔兰籍天主教徒住家男人
Top of his class, devout Irish Catholic, family man.
显示他有强烈的责任感
Everything in his profile indicates a fierce sense of duty.
那是维持他生存的要素
That's probably what kept him alive.
恕我直言 你的专长是心理学
With due respect, Dr. Faxx, your area of expertise is psychology.
不是机械人
Not robotics.
不妨听听她说 对不对
There's no harm in hearing the young lady out, is there?
是的
No, sir.
谢谢 我相信亚历克斯·墨菲的情况是不寻常但并非罕见
Thank you, sir. I believe that Murphy's case was unusual but not unique.
我们可另觅人选 一个甚至让前景变得...
We can find someone else, someone to whom the prospect might even be...
合意的人
...desirable.
我从没见过有人想做机械人的
I've never met anyone who wanted to be a robot.
要经过筛选 我乐意负责监督
It would require a screening process, one I'd would be happy to supervise.
成本可能是很少
The cost would be negligible.
浪费那方面的工作会很可惜
It would be a shame to waste all the work that's been done.
当然是的
It certainly would.
进行吧 直接向我报告
Go to it. Report to me directly.
知道
Yes, sir.
你可以从她身上学到一点东西
You could learn a thing or two from that girl, Johnson.
我可不会
not for me!
给良好警察 良好待遇
Decent pay to decent cops!
工会有一张名单 我们不会放过你
Union's got a list! We ain't forgetting who you are!
逐个说
One at a time!
麻烦你 逐个说
Please, one at a time.
你们不知道这里的情况吗
Don't you know what's going on out here?
我们已经尽了力
It's the best we can do!
小姐们 你好
Hello, ladies!
他们不能再袭击警察
They won't be fucking with any more cops!
他们不能再惹任何人
They won't be fucking with nobody, man!
(重播)
何博 就是他
Hob. That's him.
谢谢
Thank you.
给我核灵
Nuke me!
来吧 拿两支
Go ahead. Take two.
有很多货
There's plenty of Nuke to go around.
他走丢了
I've lost him.
你很久没有来了
You haven't been around in a while.
我请客
Go ahead. This one's on me.
西南偏南五度
Five degrees south-southwest.
找到那个小子了
There's the little darling.
眼睛很锐利呢
Good eyes, Murphy.
锐利得很
Good as money can buy.
费迪 你出 来了
Ferdy, you got out.
我会告诉勒恩
Well, I'll tell Cain, okay?
这次最好给我一点情报
Better have something to give me this time, officer.
每辆车有一个警察 这些是路线
One cop per car. Okay, these are the routes.
有三辆车
Three cars.
- 每辆车有一个警察  - 对
- One cop per car?  - That's right.
作为射击目标 我们安排了三个狙击手
Sitting ducks. We set up three snipers and that's all it takes.
- 付钱给他  - 好的
- Pay the man.  - All right.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 你没有点算  - 不用了
- You didn't count it.  - That's all right.
你该点算一下
You should really count it, you know.
不用了
It's okay.
给他一点东西 减轻他良心的悔疚吧
Give him something to help him with his conscience.
不用了 我不要它
No, that's all right. I don't really want it.
来吧 杜飞 我知道你需要它
Come on, Duffy. I know you need it.
今天不是要上学吗
Isn't this a school day?
警察
Cops!
该死
Oh, shit!
不好了
Oh, no.
别动
Freeze!
转过身来 举高双手
Turn around. Put your hands up.
该死
Shit.
杜飞探员 请坐
Officer Duffy, have a seat.
婊子 你好像没气了
You look a little out of breath, bitch.
- 杜飞探员 你出卖我们  - 什么意思
- You sold us out, Officer Duffy.  - What are you talking about, Murph?
勒恩在哪里
Where is Cain?
我不认识什么勒恩
I don't know any Cain.
勒恩在哪里
Where is Cain?
我不知道
I don't know.
勒恩在哪里
Where is Cain?!
我说过我不知道
I told you, I don't know!
在哪里
Where?
在鲁兹河那间旧矿泥工厂
River Rouge. The old sludge plant.
你是个腐败的警察
You're a rotten cop.
（私家重地 闲人免进）
去吧
Go.
- 你  - 你要我
- You.  - You want me?
不管死活
Dead or alive.
我们其中一个要死了
Then one of us must die.
那么死吧
Dead, then.
天啊...
Jesus...
竟有这样的日子
...had days like this.
像个罪犯般被追捕和袭击
Hounded and attacked like a criminal.
但像他一样 我不怪责你
But like him, I don't blame you.
他们给你输入程式 你照着做
They program you, and you do it.
- 我会杀了你  - 试试吧
- I will kill you.  - Oh, you just tried.
而且...
And...
我原谅你
...I forgive you.
干嘛停手 你把它砸开
Why'd you stop? You got it cracked.
我很累
I'm tired.
他们说他有脑袋 我要看
They say he's got a brain. I want to see it.
你以为是我打你
You think it was me that beat you?
不是
It wasn't.
是这个
It was this.
它太硬了
It's too tough.
在关节位置试试
Try here at the joint.
对
Yeah!
看
Look at that!
来吧 凿开它
Come on. Cut it out.
滋味怎样
How's it taste?
到底什么事
What the hell's going on?!
天 看他
Man, just look at him.
他被拆开了
Christ, he's been stripped.
我们别感情用事 它只是一件机器
Let's not get carried away here. We're talking about a piece of equipment.
别告诉我他不能受苦
Don't tell me he can't suffer.
看看他
Just look at him.
是电力作用
It's electrical.
胡说
Bullshit.
我清楚他的每一英吋 每条电路
I know every inch of him. Every circuit.
每条活神经
Every living nerve.
他的痛楚中枢是活的 活跃得像亮了灯的圣诞树
His pain centers are alive. They're lit up like Christmas trees.
后备发电机令他抽搐
The back-up generator's just making him twitch.
他很痛苦
He's suffering.
他可以熬多久
How long can he last?
没法知道
No way of knowing.
这是最低度的维持生命装置
Got him on minimal life support.
靠微震维持脑部功能
Keeping the brain going with microshocks.
- 很棘手 他随时会死亡  - 走 快走
- It's damn tricky. He could go anytime.  - Move. Move!
这里发生什么事
What's happening in here?
OCP的事 OCP的混蛋们一点也不肯帮他
OCP is happening. These bastards won't lift a finger to help him.
这个单位需要数百万元的零件
This unit needs millions of dollars in parts.
我不能一夜间批核那笔费用 请讲讲道理
You can't expect authorization for that kind of cash overnight. Be reasonable.
若你不修理他 就是谋杀
If you don't fix him, it's murder.
冷静点 我跟你谈是给你恩惠了
Settle down. I'm doing you a favor by talking to you.
你这个混蛋 他很痛苦
You son of a bitch. He's in hell.
修理他
Fix him!
我们会保持联络
We'll be in touch.
你们是最了不起的
Oh, man, you guys are the greatest!
你可看到他们的脸
Did you see their faces?
"我们会抛掉那锁匙 杜飞"
"We're gonna throw away the key, Duffy."
警方可有给你麻烦
The cops didn't give you trouble, did they?
李约翰惯常的废话 他们证明不到什么的
The usual shit from Reed. They'll never prove anything.
喝一点吗
Hey, want some?
我是个小孩 我不想犯法
Hey, I'm a minor. Don't want to break any laws.
你拿着吧
Here, you take it.
我真喜欢你们
God, I just love you guys!
什么事
What happened?
我们去哪里
Hey, where we going?
别这样 这样不好玩
Hey, come on, guys. This isn't funny, man.
天啊 我的头
Oh, God, my head.
我的头很痛
My head is killing me.
老兄 到底...
Hey, man. What's...
勒恩 看到你真好
Hey, Cain! Hey, it's good to see you.
谢谢你救我
Thanks for getting me out.
- 我不能起来  - 我们知道
- I can't get up.  - You noticed that one.
- 我不知道那个孩子对你说什么  - 你告诉他们
- Cain, I don't know what the kid told you...  - You told them, Duffy.
- 你告诉他们我们在哪里  - 没有
- You told them where we were.  - That's not true.
- 我们全都知道  - 你以为我们只有你一个警察
- We know all about it, Duffy.  - You think you're the only cop we have?
该死
Oh, shit!
勒恩 求求你
Cain. Cain, come on. Man, I'm begging you, man!
我什么也愿意做
Look, I'll do anything!
你说笑吧 对 你在说笑
Okay. You're kidding, right? Yeah, you're just kidding.
你吓怕我了 你给了我一个教训
You scared me. You taught me a lesson, man.
我不会耍你们 因为我很喜欢你们的
I'd never fuck with you, because I really love you guys.
- 真的  - 闭嘴
- I really do!  - Shut up!
我一直很忠心 我还有一些内幕消息没告诉你们
I've been loyal. I know shit that I still haven't even told you, Cain!
你是罪有应得的 勒恩差点没命
You deserve this, Duffy. Cain might have been killed.
好
Okay.
你应该叫那个孩子离开
Maybe you ought to have the kid leave.
- 为什么  - 叫那个孩子离开是什么意思
- Why?  - What do you mean, "have the kid leave"?
真有特色"叫那个孩子离开"
That's a good touch. That's a good touch."Have the kid leave."
"叫那个孩子离开" 为什么
That's good."Have the kid leave." Why?
别这样 闹完了
Come on. It's over.
勒恩 别这样 你做什么
Come on, Cain! Come on, man. What are you doing?
别这样
Come on!
你说你只会吓他一下
You said you were just gonna scare him!
他不是很害怕吗
Doesn't he look scared?
难以置信你竟然这样做
I can't believe you'd do this.
申先生 你相信什么都不要紧
It hardly matters what you believe, Mr. Schenk.
但这些是罪犯 他们是狂人
But these are criminals. They're maniacs.
你太早作判断了
You're giving premature value judgments.
不错 这些人可能是误入歧途
All right, it may be true. The subjects are socially misaligned.
误入歧途 这些都是死囚
Socially misaligned? These are death row inmates!
而且对社会毫无用处 我们要找一个...
And of no use to society. We need a subject who'll welcome the power...
愿意接受力量以及永生的人
...the virtual immortality we offer.
我相信这里是寻找合适者的好地方
Now, I really think this is a good place to start looking.
- 你是疯的  - 这是否你的专业意见
- You're out of your mind.  - Is that your professional opinion?
是的 不错
Yes, goddamn it, it is! Yes!
你不能用我的实验室 把那样的脑袋放进我的半机械人
And you are not using my lab to put that kind of a brain into my cyborg.
我们会很怀念你的
We'd dearly miss you here.
你才会失业
You're the one that's gonna be out of a job.
我会直接找强生说这件事
I'm going to take this directly to Johnson.
他正等待着藉口要把你开除
He's just been waiting for an excuse to get you fired.
老板早
Good morning, sir.
抱歉这么早打扰你
I'm sorry to bother you this early.
你看来很不安
You seem agitated.
坦白说 我很震惊
Frankly, I'm shocked.
申先生刚打电话来
Mr. Schenk just called.
费博士已经开始筛选做机械警察二号计划的人选
Dr. Faxx has begun screening candidates for the Robocop 2 project...
我也知道 很令人兴奋呢
So I understand. It's very exciting.
他在挑选一些神经病 杀人凶手
She's screening psychotics, sir. Murderers.
我们不是计划制造一件玩具
We aren't planning to build a toy, Johnson.
费知道她自己在做什么
Faxx knows what she's doing.
她要机械警察停止活动 那是个公关大灾难
She's keeping Robocop offline. It's a public-relations disaster.
你要为大局着想 那个取消赎回权...
You've got to learn to look at the larger picture. The foreclosure.
对我们很重要的
You must know how important that is to us.
机械警察停止执勤 外面的混乱会升级
With Robocop out of commission, the chaos down there will increase...
本市就有机会落在我们手上
...and the odds the city will fall into our hands.
但一个胜任的行政人员就能解决公司的形象问题
But a competent executive would find a way to deal with the corporate image problem.
我非常同意 强生先生
Couldn't agree with you more, Mr. Johnson.
幸好我已经找到方法
Fortunately, I have found a way.
对 我和费小姐已经讨论过了
Yes, Ms. Faxx and I have already discussed it.
我知道你会协助执行她的构思
I know you'll help to implement her ideas.
当然 我会尽力
Of course, sir. Whatever I can do.
还有什么
Anything else?
- 要咖啡吗  - 不 谢谢
- Coffee?  - No, thank you.
出去时别忘了穿回鞋子
Don't forget your shoes on the way out.
他是我的病人而且垂危 我要陪着他
He's my patient and critical. I must stay with him.
我们有需要时会找你
We'll let you know when we need you.
没有人比我更认识他 你们需要我的
Nobody on your staff has my experience with him. You need me.
我们不需要任何人
We don't need anybody.
谁是"我们" 你是个无知的律师
"We". Who the hell are "we"? You're a lawyer who knows nothing!
你快要被开除了
You're exactly this far from getting fired, babe.
蔡斯达
Shyster!
他是我的人
He's one of mine.
我要他复原过来
I want him back on his feet.
可能会吧 或者我们会把零件作废料出售
Maybe he will be, or maybe we'll just sell the parts for scrap.
要视乎我们了
That's up to us.
机械警察过了保用期了
You see, Robocop's off warranty.
机械警察的指令程式...
Robocop's command program...
他的一套指示...
...his set of directives...
决定他的行为 是时候更新那套程式了
It determines his behavior. It's time to update the program...
我想听听各位的意见
...and I would like to hear from each one of you.
是时候他们咨询我们了
It's about time they asked us.
我们收到很多家长团体的反对
We're getting a lot of heat from parents' groups.
我不怪责他们 我也是个家长
Personally, I don't blame them. I'm a parent.
那些破坏性的行为
All that destructive behavior.
他成了我们孩子的榜样
He's become a role model for our children.
- 我们在教他们什么  - 说得有理
- Now, what are we teaching them?  - You have a point.
如果他可以说道理而不随便开枪
If he talked things out with people instead of firing that gun.
他可否花点时间应付环保问题
Couldn't he take a little time to address environmental issues?
什么
What was that?
他可以发表环保上的意见
He could speak out on environmental issues.
可以的
Don't see any reason why not.
他除了开枪
For all the shooting he does...
我从没看过他做点好事
I've never once seen him take the time to do anything nice...
- 譬如探访孤儿院  - 你说得对
- like visit an orphanage.  - You're absolutely right.
或者在树上拯救猫儿
Or help a cat out of a tree...
或替红十字会收集捐款
or go door to door collecting for the Red Cross...
或者跟童子军一起烧棉花糖
...or maybe even roasting some marshmallows with some Cub Scouts.
强生先生 那主意不错 谢谢你
Why, Mr. Johnson, that is wonderful. Thank you so much.
- 程式还没输入  - 他在抗拒
- It's no good. The program isn't uploading.  - He's resisting.
太多资料了
There's too much data.
- 不 是他 让我来吧  - 我不可以 不行的
- No, it's him. Leave him to me, Schenk.  - I can't... It's not going to work!
你在浪费宝贵时间
You're wasting valuable time.
- 不要抗拒我们  - 让我起来
- Don't resist us.  - Let me up.
我一定要去
I must go.
去哪里
Go where?
做什么 跳舞 谈恋爱 你以为自己是什么
Do what? Go dancing? Fall in love? What is it you think you are?
亚历克斯·墨菲
Alex Murphy.
那是个错觉
That's a delusion.
那是你系统里的故障 亚历克斯·墨菲已经死了
It's a glitch in your system. Alex Murphy is dead.
拿掉那些金属和电线 你只是桌上的一堆东西
Take away the metal and wires, you're just a couple chunks on a table.
你甚至不是个尸体
You're not even a corpse.
你是什么
What are you?
回答
Respond.
我是亚历克斯·墨菲探员
I am Officer Alex Murphy...
底特律警察部
...Detroit Police Department.
不行
That won't do.
你是什么
What are you?
机械警察 防止罪案组
Robocop. Crime Prevention Unit.
OCP
OCP.
好多了 ...
Better. Much better.
我输入什么 你就想什么
I type it. You think it.
你输入什么我就想什么
You type it. I think it.
你代表着一个大好机会
What a wonderful opportunity you represent.
心理治疗 是这么的...
Psychotherapy, it's such a...
原本是缓慢 笨拙的过程 但用在你身上就简单得很
It's a slow, clumsy practice. But with you this is so simple.
直接
Direct.
你很幸运
You're lucky.
你可在短时间内完成人类病人几年的疗程
We can do in moments with you what would take years with a human patient.
我真的很幸运
I'm really very lucky.
你不用怀疑 也不用作痛苦的抉择
You're free. You're free from doubt. Free from having to make painful choices.
我很自由
I am free.
他准备好了
He's ready.
输入指令程式
Uploading command program.
我很高兴我们有这个机会对话
I am so glad we had this chance to dialogue.
你看起来像全新一样
Look at you. It's like you're brand-new.
过奖
Thank you. Thank you.
我们很担心你呢
You really had us worried there, Murphy.
我很感动
I'm touched.
看这个家伙
Get this guy.
他很感动
He's touched.
够了 大家回岗位 快点
That's enough. All of you, back to your posts. Come on. Let's go.
墨菲 你怎样
How you feeling, Murphy?
我很好 谢谢关心
I'm just fine, Warren. Thank you for asking.
我们带你到楼下去
Let's get you downstairs.
我要看看OCP那班外行弄得怎样一团糟
I want to see what those amateurs at OCP screwed up.
可惜 这是个可爱的早上
Pity. It's a beautiful morning.
浪费它真可惜
Shame to waste it.
- 拍档 准备出勤了吗  - 当然
- Ready for duty, partner?  - You betcha.
- 我们走吧  - 我很渴望呢
- Let's go.  - Nothing I'd rather do.
他听来很好
He sounds terrific.
有问题
Something's wrong.
大力一点
Harder!
机械警察来了 大家快从后门走
It's Robo! Everybody out the back door!
- 它锁上了  - 打不开
- It's locked!  - It won't open!
墨菲 醒一醒
Murph, wake up, will you?
早安
Good morning.
来吧 对付他
Come on, take him out.
我们应该谈一下
I think we should talk.
你有什么问题
What's with you, Murph?
- 他们去了哪里 - "他们去了哪里"
- Where'd they go?  - "Where'd they go?"
那些小混蛋还在这里
They're still here, the little bastards!
举手 来吧 大家站起来
Hands up! Let's go! Everybody up!
快点 靠着墙壁
Move it. Up against the wall.
快点
Let's go.
双手放在头上 不准动
Hands on top of your heads. Nobody move.
你被拘捕了
You are under arrest.
你有权保持缄默
You have the right to remain silent.
但你所说的一切会在法庭...
Anything you say can and will be used against you...
- 成为呈堂证供  - 墨菲 他死了
- ...in a court of law.  - He's dead, Murphy.
- 你有权...  - 你在向死尸背诵拘捕法则
- You have the right...  - You're reading Miranda to a corpse!
我有麻烦
I'm having trouble.
天啊
Oh, my.
这样不太好
This isn't very nice.
虽然你们可能觉得很有趣
Though you may think you're having fun now...
但你们只会令爱你们的人伤心
...you only hurt the one you love.
想想爸妈
Think of Mom and Dad.
你在教他们什么
What kind of lesson are you teaching them?
现在谈一下营养吧
And now, a word on nutrition.
他妈的 他搞砸了
Shit! He's fucked up!
粗言秽语有损感情
Bad language makes for bad feelings.
我们走吧
Let's go!
问题是...
The point is...
我们都要工作
...we all have to work.
我还没说完
I haven't finished.
墨菲 开快点
Hit the gas, Murphy.
车速限制是35
The posted limit is 35.
我们该作榜样的 安妮
We should set an example, Anne.
你的发型很好看
Your hair looks lovely that way.
是OCP 他们给你做了手脚
It's OCP. They did something to you.
我很好
I'm fine.
今晚的月色不错吧
Isn't the moon wonderful tonight?
现在还是白天
It's still daytime.
心意才是最重要的
It's the thought that counts.
天啊 我们要回警察局 就这样
Oh, Jesus, we're heading back to the station. That's all there is to it.
你们干什么
What the hell are you doing?!
一寸光阴...
Waste makes haste...
一寸金
...for time is fleeting.
寸金难买寸光阴
A rolling stone is worth two in the bush.
去搞个雪柜吧 蠢才
Go fuck a refrigerator, pecker neck!
粗言秽语有损感情的
Bad language makes for bad feelings.
你是个傻瓜
You're nuts!
墨菲 我们走吧
Murphy, come on, let's go.
走吧
Come on!
（踢我）
退后
Back!
谢谢你不吸烟
Thank you for not smoking.
对了 是OCP
Well, there it is. It's OCP.
他们把他弄坏了
They screwed him up.
他一定是疯了
He must be going out of his mind.
他不能就这样说不的
It's not as if he can just say no.
他们把一些废话输入他的脑袋 他要服从
They put all this nonsense into his brain. He has to obey.
把它们全部洗掉吧
Take them out, all of them!
靠这副仪器做不来的
Can't be done, not with this equipment.
你说没有办法 我不能相信
Are you saying there's no way? I can't believe that.
当然有办法 你可以截断他头颅的线路
Sure, there are ways. You can pull his cranial circuits.
那会关掉他的生命维持器
Which would shut down his life-support.
你可以用几千伏特电流通过他全身
You could run a few thousand volts through him.
可能会把他杀死
Probably kill him.
我去找人来帮忙
I'll get some help!
- 扶他进去  - 快点
- Get him inside!  - Come on, move it!
- 快点  - 别碰他 他很热的
- Come on!  - Don't touch him, he's hot!
用你们的外衣
Use your jackets.
干嘛他要那样做
Why'd he do that?
他烧毁自己来解除OCP的指令
Fried himself to get rid of OCP's crazy commands.
- 慢慢来  - 他很重
- Nice and easy.  - He weighs a ton.
让开 走开
Out of the way! Move out!
- 他还活着吗  - 他很热
- Think he's alive?  - I don't know. He's pretty hot.
放下我
Put me down.
(列出指令)
(搜寻中...)
扶他站起来
All right. Come on, stand him up.
(没有指令)
我们是不是警察
Are we cops?
你在烦什么
What's bugging you, Murph?
勒恩
Cain.
我在烦勒恩
Cain's bugging me.
手足们 这只是开始
We have only just begun, my flock.
我们不久便会在各个城市扩张
Soon we will expand from city to city.
富人和穷人生命里的每一刻...
The rich and poor alike will know a paradise...
都会置身天堂
...for every moment of their lives.
这是每种情绪的核灵
This is a Nuke for every mood.
我们会提供给他们...
We'll offer the opportunity...
控制各种情绪的机会
...to control every aspect of their emotional lives.
这里有白色声浪和黑色雷暴...
Here with the white noise and black thunder...
还有红色输弹机和蓝色丝绒
...and the red ramrod and the blue velvet.
法兰克 蓝色丝绒
Frank. The blue velvet.
它准备好了
I think it's ready, sir.
谢谢你
Thank you, Frank.
那苯甲胺令我牙关扭动
Frank. The Benzedrine's got my teeth wiggling.
用莨菪碱代替它
Cut it with scopolamine.
- 每支五毫升  - 知道
- Five mils per.  - Yes, sir.
美国制造
Made in America.
那又再有意义了
Yeah. We're gonna make that mean something again.
- 有警察  - 什么
- Hey! Cops!  - What?
警察
Cops!
他们没有挂罢工牌的
And they ain't carrying no picket signs!
他们去捉人呢
They're going to kick somebody's ass!
把你的手给我
Give me your hand, goddamn it!
天啊
Christ!
他妈的
Fuck!
快走
Get out!
有炸弹 伏下
Bomb! Get down!
混蛋
You son of a bitch!
警方搜出贩卖核灵 所得的五亿元赃款
Five hundred million in cash. Nuke money seized by police.
但州检察官不准破产的市政府碰它
But State Attorney Sphincter won't let the bankrupt city government touch it.
下一节报导警员工会作出威胁警察恢复执勤...
Coming up next, threats from the police union and cheers from the public...
和拘捕核灵毒枭勒恩令市民欢呼
...as Metro-North cops go back to work and apprehend the Nuke lord, Cain...
勒恩可能活不到受审
...who may not live to stand trial.
（加州 比华利山）
人们说自从失去了臭氧层 ...
They say 20 seconds in the California sunshine...
现在在加州晒20秒太阳
...is too much these days...
已经太久了
...ever since we lost the ozone layer.
但那是在抗晒5000面世之前
But that was before Sunblock 5000.
只要你在身上...
Just apply a pint...
涂一品脱
...to your body...
便能持续数小时
...and you're good for hours.
在游泳池边见吧
See you by the pool.
抗晒5000
Sunblock 5000.
新纪元的保障
Protection for the new age.
实验人选是暴力反社会分子
Subject is violently antisocial...
自诩为神
...given to delusions of godhood.
他有极深的毒瘾
And he's hopelessly addicted to narcotics.
这会提供一个简单而可靠的方法...
Which offers us a simple and infallible method...
去保证他的服从性
...of insuring his obedience.
你是完美的
You're perfect.
我一定要得到你
I must have you.
你说什么 你好像全不在乎
What are you talking about? It's like you don't even care!
- 照我的话做  - 他要我们对付他
- Just do what I say, Angie!  - He'd want us to come for him!
算了 不会发生的 我不想跟你争吵
Forget about it! It's not gonna happen! I'm through arguing with you!
我不是要求批准 他在医院 我们要救他
I'm not asking permission! Cain is in the hospital, and we're getting him.
你也考虑过这件事 那些警察又如何
You've really thought this out, haven't you? What about the cops?
我们有枪 勒恩需要我们
We've got guns! Damn it, Hob, Cain needs us!
去他的勒恩
Fuck Cain!
- 你那样说他会杀死你的  - 他谁也不会杀
- He'd kill you if he heard you.  - He's not gonna kill anybody!
- 可能他已经死了  - 闭嘴
- Shit, he's probably dead already.  - You just shut the hell up!
婊子 再吵就不给你核灵
You mouth off like that again, and it's no more Nuke for you, bitch.
该死 那是不公平的
Damn it, Hob, you know that's not fair.
别这样
Now, come on.
- 我很难过  - 对 你很伤心
- It's been a bad time.  - Sure has. You're really hurting.
是的
Yeah, so I'm hurting.
你很快会克服的
You're gonna get the shakes soon, Angie.
很快克服
You got it bad.
你这个混蛋
You little bastard.
以后你依我的说话做
You just do what I tell you from now on, Angie.
开车吧
Start the motor and drive.
他会杀你的
He'll kill you.
他会杀我们
He'll kill us both.
去他的
Fuck him.
你糟透了
Oh, you're a mess.
我有好消息
I got good news for you.
你有一个永生的机会
You're going to have a chance for immortality.
只要那个可爱的脑袋没有受损
As long as nothing happens to that lovely brain.
韦文医生 我是茱莉·费
Dr. Weltman? It's Faxx.
我们的病人死了
I'm afraid we lost our patient.
是 他刚死了
Yeah, he just expired.
叫器官切除组来 在脑袋失效前我们有六分钟
Contact the organ harvest team. We've got six minutes before the brain's useless.
晚安
Night.
快点动手 我们只有五分钟
Come on. Let's move it. We've only got five minutes.
锁上它
Lock it up.
把荧幕移近一点 我看不到它
Move the screen in closer. I can't read it.
- 怎样找到这个的  - 费找到他的
- How'd we get this one?  - Well, Faxx found him.
他自愿的
He volunteered.
自愿
Volunteered?
好心的家伙
Big-hearted guy.
对 但我们不是要他的心脏
Yeah, it's not the heart we're after, though.
说起心脏 艾莲怎样了
Speaking of hearts, how's Ilene?
天啊 大家都知道吗
Christ, does everybody know?
好了 屏气凝神
All right, hold your breath.
出场了
Showtime.
这里完整干净 没有受伤
It's nice and clean in here. There's no damage.
来吧
Here we go.
慢慢来
Easy.
行了 来了
We got it. Here it comes.
- 好东西  - 很好
- Thing of beauty.  - Excellent.
我不知道你们怎样 但我很饿了
I don't know about the rest of you, but I'm hungry.
（底特律: 协助拯救汽车之城）
谢谢
Thank you!
对
Yes!
蜘蛛宝贝施莱基
Spider Baby Stalirski!
他为底特律出力 现在你们为他出力
He's come out for Detroit, and now you come out for him.
多条电话线等着接听你们
The lines are open, waiting for your pledge.
若你想要一个诚实的政府...
If you want an honest government...
为你做事
...that works for you...
我请求你慷慨解囊
...I'm asking you to dig deep into your pockets.
我请求你...
I'm asking you to give...
随缘乐捐
...whatever you can spare!
数目有多少了
Where does that put us?
（我们的目标是37,480,911 收款是4,823）
你好 是 小姐
Hi. Yes, ma'am.
你好 我是古泽市长
Hello! This is Mayor Kuzak!
麻烦你调低电视机的声浪
Could you turn down your set, please?
市长
Your Honor...
我有好消息给你
...I have some very good news for you.
我相信...
I think...
本市得救了
...the city is saved.
现在...
Now...
你小心听着
...you listen very carefully.
不是吹牛的 有人会紧急援助本市
It's no bluff. Someone's shown up to bail the city out.
- 一间对手的公司  - 市长没有说
- A rival corporation.  - The mayor isn't saying.
他们要绝对让他们的身分保密
And whoever it is is taking great pains to keep their identity secret.
他们会付现金 而不是经银行汇款
They're paying in cash and they're not moving the money through the banks.
谢谢你 委员
Thank you, councilman.
就这样吧
That will be all.
当你们接管...
You know, once you guys take over...
你们给OCP的服务会得到报酬的
Your services to OCP will be rewarded.
如果市政府可以付钱 我们就很丢脸
If the city can pay, we'll be humiliated.
情况比那个更糟 我们调动八成的资源...
It's worse than that. We've shifted 80 percent of our resources...
用在那个市区的治安计划
...to the urban pacification plan.
若我们不能取消赎回权 对OCP的信心和股票都会下降
If we can't foreclose, public confidence in OCP will plummet, so will our stock.
老板
Sir?
我可否打岔
If I may?
有另一个选择
There's another option.
我们派监视装备跟踪市长
We certainly have the surveillance capabilities to follow the mayor.
视乎我们愿意做多少工夫
It all depends how far we're willing to go.
如果发生问题...
If anything went wrong...
正如我所说...
As I said, sir...
视乎我们愿意做多少工夫
...it all depends how far we're willing to go.
我们没有索偿权
We have no legal recourse.
不可以有目击证人
There must be no witnesses.
你太过分了 给我...
You've gone too far! Give me...
你的血压
Your blood pressure.
开除我好了 我的实验室里不可有非法毒品
Get me fired if you want to. You're not bringing illegal drugs to my lab!
我不单只会开除你 别理会我
I'll do worse than get you fired. Now leave me alone!
多么可怕的痛楚
Such terrible pain.
你不记得我
You don't remember me.
但你记得这个吧
But you do remember this, don't you?
我们有它 你要多少核灵都有
And we have it. All the Nuke you'll ever need.
慢一点
Not so fast.
我要你先替我做一件事
I need you to do something for me first.
然后痛楚就会停止
Then the pain stops.
乖孩子
Good boy.
我不喜欢这样 我们还是走吧
I don't like this. I think we'd better get out of here while we can.
我知道我在做什么
I know what I'm doing.
你有现钞的话 把它放进内裤吧
If you have any cash, put it in your shorts.
那真是无礼
That's just plain rude.
你可否帮我
I wonder if any of you could help me.
我想找何博先生
I'm looking for a Mr. Hob.
那么...
So...
你要多少
...how much you need?
我是指钱
Money, I mean.
我们现在欠OCP...
Well, our current debt to OCP is...
37,480,911元
$37,480,911 dollars.
你有大麻烦了
Guess you're in some pretty deep shit.
我们需要大量的资助
We need all the help we can get, young man.
记下我给五十吧
Tell you what. Put me down for 50, just to make sure.
- 五角 五十元 真可爱  - 别做傻瓜
- 50 cents, 50 dollars. That's cute.  - Don't be a queer.
是五千万
Fifty million.
胡说八道 我们走吧
This is bullshit. Let's get out of here.
（危险 拆炸弹小组）
天啊
Good God.
各位
Gentlemen?
五千万够吗
Well, will 50 do it?
够 可以了
Oh, yes. That'll do it.
- 你认为够吗  - 够了
- Don't you guys think that'll do it?  - Yeah.
五千万 够了
Fifty mil. That will do it.
- 够了  - 这些人是罪犯
- That'll do it.  - These people are criminals!
为何你给人家定标签 我讨厌标签
Why do you have to label people? I hate labels!
闭嘴
You shut up.
在灭罪的斗争中我们不能屈从
We cannot capitulate in the war on crime.
我会丢掉官职的 我相信没有人想那样
I'd be voted out of office. I don't think anyone wants that.
我们不反对灭罪
War on crime is fine with us.
我们说的是生意
It's business we're talking about here.
你可知道我们雇用多少人
Do you have any idea how many people we employ?
不知道 我从没有想过
No. I never thought about it like that.
精明的孩子
Sharp kid.
那么...
So...
灭罪的斗争...
...your war on crime...
你想不想赢
...you want to win it or what?
我们是你唯一的机会
We're the only chance you have.
听他说
Listen to him.
他有全盘大计
He's got it all worked out.
为什么人们犯罪
Why do people do crimes?
- 为什么 人们吸毒  - 因为他们要毒品
- Why? Drugs. People do drugs.  - Because they want drugs.
要那种贵价货
The kind that cost too much.
核灵价廉物美
Nuke gives high quality at a cheap price.
如果你不干涉我们 我们会卖得更便宜
If you get off our backs, we'll make it cheaper.
和更安全
And safer.
我们没有强迫人家吸食我们的货
We don't shove our shit down anybody's throat.
也没有像香烟洋酒般卖广告
And we don't advertise it like they do with cigarettes or booze.
所以别管我们
So leave us alone...
也别管要买它的人
...and anybody who wants it gets it.
那就再没有罪案了
So no more crimes.
你会是整顿底特律的市长
You get to be the mayor who cleaned up Detroit.
他说得有理
He's got a point.
你认为是不是
Don't you think he's got a point?
是 他有道理
Yeah, he's got a point.
那是什么
What the hell is that?
快走
Get out!
市长 你...
Marv, are...
(身分搜寻: 市长与目击者)
(记忆)
勒恩
Cain.
厉害
Oh, wow.
你看来很好
You look great.
我要习惯一下...
It'll take some getting used to...
但这样会很好的
...but it'll be great, Cain.
躺着别动
Lie still.
- 我很冻  - 你会休克
- I'm cold.  - You are going into shock.
我会找急救医疗队来
I will call for a medical emergency unit.
等一下 不
Wait. No.
不要丢下我
Don't leave me.
我不会丢下你
I won't leave you.
是谁做的
Who did this?
它很大呢
It was big.
比你还大
Bigger than you.
是勒恩
It was Cain.
我快要死了
I'm gonna die.
你知道那是怎样的吧
You know what that's like, don't you?
真是难受
It really sucks.
是的
Yes.
在一宗核灵赃款大屠杀里有13人死亡
Thirteen dead in what appears to be a Nuke money massacre.
死者当中有两名市政府委员
Among the victims, two city councilmen.
市政府是否想勾结大毒枭
Was the city trying to strike a deal with the drug lords?
无可奉告 我说无可奉告
No comment! I said, I have no comment!
我对这些指控无可奉告
No comments on these allegations.
这些人孜孜不倦的服务本市
These were men who served this city tirelessly.
但我向底特律市民承诺
However, I make a promise to the people of Detroit City...
我们会全力以赴彻底调查这件事
...that no effort will be spared to investigate this thoroughly!
但是市长 那个...
But, Mr. Mayor, what about...
抱歉 不要再问了
I'm sorry. No more questions.
我们的古泽市长
Our own Mayor Kuzak.
现在看杰西的现场报导
Now let's go live to Jess.
这是OCP赠予本市 楼高一百层的市府大楼
And here it is, the Civic Centrum, OCP's 100-story gift to the Motor City.
尽管OCP的敌意收购持续引起争议
While debate continues over OCP's hostile takeover...
这里的气氛却很热闹
...there's no denying the mood down here is festive.
受访问的市民都表示兴奋
Citizens interviewed on the scene expressed excitement and hope...
还希望OCP会兑现改善本市生活的承诺
...that OCP will make good on its promise of a better life in Detroit.
- 记者  - 抱歉 只限传媒
- Press!  - Sorry, folks, media only.
只限电视台和报馆你们要退后
TV and press only. You'll have to step back.
他来了
There he is!
OCP能否重振底特律的工业
Can OCP bring industry back to Detroit?
OCP是否拥有本市 你可会举行大选
Does OCP own the city? Will you hold elections?
- 我们是否成为OCP的雇员  - 为何不去大会堂
- Do we become OCP employees?  - Why not go to City Hall?
等一会
Just a minute.
小姐 我会回答这问题
I'll answer that, young lady.
大会堂是管理不善和腐败的象征
City Hall is the decaying symbol of mismanagement and corruption.
你拍到了吗
You get that?
这座宏伟的建筑物是新领导的所在
This magnificent structure will be the seat of leadership for the new Detroit.
可不是个廉洁新开始的好地方
And what better place for a clean, fresh start?
各位报界朋友...
And so, people of the press...
市政府官员
...city officials...
在一息间普及消费者产品...
...in a few minutes Omni Consumer Products...
和动乱的底特律市...
...and the troubled city of Detroit...
会携手共创新里程
...will join in a bold new venture.
现在我想解释一下...
Now I'd like to explain...
这件事的意义
...just what this will mean.
有时候我们要...
Sometimes we just have to start over...
从头开始...
...from scratch...
去修正事情
...to make things right.
这正是我们要做的事
And that's exactly what we're going to do.
我们会兴建一个全新的城市
We're going to build a brand-new city...
座落在目前的底特律市
...where Detroit now stands.
一个全世界...
An example...
的榜样
...to the world.
各位朋友...
My friends...
欢迎到来我们原来就该有的城市
...welcome to our city as it should be.
它也会落在负责任的...
And as it will be, in the hands of responsible...
私人企业的手上
...private enterprise.
请欢迎...
And a special welcome...
古泽市长和即将离任的官员
...to Mayor Kuzak and the outgoing administration.
我们不会离开的
We're not going anywhere.
市长
Your Honor.
你们要拆毁很多房屋才兴建到那个的
You'll have to tear down a lot of houses to make that.
拆毁家园
I mean, take away their homes!
我们会兴建玻璃和钢铁的大厦
We're going to raise towers of glass and steel.
每个市民都会有一间 安全 干净的居所
Every citizen will have a living unit, safe, secure, and clean.
请你坐下
Now, please take your seat.
没有多少空间作邻舍设施
Won't be much room for neighborhoods.
不像我们成长的环境
Not like the kind we all grew up in.
今天邻舍是罪恶的温床
Today neighborhoods are places where bad things happen.
不要怀旧了
Don't be nostalgic.
民主呢 没有人选过你
What about democracy? Nobody elected you.
任何人都可以购买OCP股票
Anyone can buy OCP stock...
和拥有本市的一部分
...and own a piece of our city.
有什么比那个更民主
What could be more democratic than that?
本市有很多人都买不起你们的股票
There's a lot of people in this town that can't afford to buy your stock!
他们也不会让你得逞的
And they won't let you get away with this.
你一直没有关注民意
You haven't been following the polls.
坐下
Sit down.
市长 坐下吧
Sit down, mayor.
一年前我们给了本市机械警察
About a year ago we gave this city Robocop.
他的表现很好
I think he's worked out pretty well.
但外面的治安越来越差
But things have become rougher out there.
现在我们需要一个执法者...
And now we need a law enforcement unit...
他可以亲身对付敌人
...able to meet the enemy on his own ground...
携带足够的火力 ...
...and carrying enough firepower...
把任务完成
...to get the job done.
各位来宾...
Ladies and gentlemen...
我很高兴...
...with great pleasure...
为大家介绍...
...I give you...
机械警察二号
...Robocop 2.
- 那些混蛋都是狂人  - 什么事
- Those bastards are maniacs!  - What's the matter?
我不能相信 是他们 他们派它去的
I can't believe it. It was them! They sent it!
派什么
Sent what?
没什么
Nothing.
这个装置将会有大量需求
There going to be a big call for this unit.
我们也会在底特律制造他
And we'll make him right here in Detroit.
那是我们可以引以为傲的工作
That means jobs we can all be proud of.
而且令"美国制造" ...
And make "Made in America"...
再有着新意义
...mean something again.
这个容器...
This single container...
盛着的核灵足以令一条街的人上瘾
...holds enough Nuke to addict a city block.
每天生产一百个
A hundred of these are produced every day...
和送到工厂去
...and sent to sweatshops...
城市劳工就在那里制这个毒品...
...where urban slaves prepare this poison...
供应我们的朋友 亲人 子女
...for our friends, our loved ones, our children.
我认为...
Now, I say...
是时候制止这个瘟疫
...it's high time we put an end to this plague.
机械警察二号会搜查每间实验室
Robocop 2 will seek out every laboratory...
每个毒贩 并且铲除市内的核灵
...every dealer, and rid our city of Nuke.
不错
Yes.
有这个家伙就会安宁多了
Things will be a lot quieter with this boy around.
- 他有什么问题  - 没事的
- What's wrong with him?  - It's nothing.
- 完全没问题  - 关掉他
- Nothing at all.  - Turn him off.
我不可以
I can't.
勒恩 我们到外面去
Cain! Let's step outside.
你 快走 你是过时的
You! Get out of here! You're obsolete!
那是个杀人凶手
That thing is a killer!
- 它没有携械 它没有杀伤力的  - 它是个凶手 我亲眼看到
- It's not even armed! It's harmless!  - It's a killer, and I saw it!
- 带她走  - 放开我
- Take her out of here! Now!  - Let me go!
你们检点一下
Behave yourselves!
(瞄准中)
- 什么事  - 天晓得 里面听来像打仗
- What's the deal here?  - Christ knows. Sounds like a war in there.
(瞄准)
你要和我同归于尽
You're coming with me, Cain.
他在那儿
There he is!
- 退后  - 你是否妒忌那个代替品
- All right, get back!  - Are you jealous of the replacement?
这样对OCP很不利
This could look bad for OCP, Johnson.
打乱我们最优秀的智囊团
Scramble the best spin team we have.
(身份 记忆)
子弹
Ammo! Ammo!
下来
Get down!
停火
Hold your fire!
Hold your fire, damn it!
快搬他走
Let's get him out of here.
小心他的头 他伤得很重
Watch his neck. He's hurt bad. Easy.
该死
Shit!
我要回去
I gotta get back.
快回去...
Move it back! Move it back!
给他要的东西吧
Let's give him what he wants.
(瞄准)
(记忆)
再见
Goodbye.
这是个麻烦 有这么多死伤者
It's serious trouble. So many dead and wounded.
死者不会构成麻烦的
There won't be trouble from the dead.
他们都有亲人的
They'll have relatives. They always do.
- 会造成大量索赔的  - 只是钱罢了
- It'll be a feeding frenzy.  - It's only money.
- 刑事诉讼又如何  - 这个...
- What about criminal proceedings?  - Well...
我们正在研究主要的起诉 就是刑期
...we're looking at major indictments, sir. Prison terms.
- 我又如何  - 我们会尽力而为的
- What about me?  - You know we'll do whatever we can.
- 那不够好  - 老板
- That's not good enough.  - Sir?
如果说这件事是个人的行为又如何
What if this was the work of one individual?
一个跟我们公司的目标不一致的人
A person who had her own agenda, wasn't in sync with the goals of our company?
那通常是可行的
Well, that usually works.
一个不合作的女人
A woman who was not a team player.
她违反了我们的信任
Who violated our trust.
放松
Easy, easy.
这个...
Well...
我们需要一些证据来支持
...we'd need some evidence to support that.
不管证据是否存在 我也找得到的
Sir, whether it exists or not, I know I can find it.
她的确挑选了那个脑袋
She did choose the brain, sir.
- 好计谋  - 老板
- Good thinking.  - Sir.
谢天谢地你平安无事
Thank God you're all right.
我很担心 我以为它会伤害你
I was worried. I thought it was going to hurt you.
事情结束了...
It's over. It's all over.
我令你失望了
I failed you.
别怪责自己 不会有事的
Don't be hard on yourself. Everything's going to be all right.
强生 我们谈的那件事
Johnson, that business we were talking about.
要马上着手进行
Get right on it.
知道
Yes, sir.
看他们弄成这个样子 他们是罪犯
Just look at what they've done. They are criminals.
我保证OCP不会拥有本市很久的
OCP won't own this city for long. And I'll see to that.
我会和市民上街示威
I'll take it to the streets and the people.
这件事有何教训
What has it come to?
商人可以像股票般收买我们的权利
Businessmen can buy our rights like stock?
你们不明白我们正在失去什么
You don't realize what we're losing!
- 先生 这里  - 发表一下
- Right here, sir!  - Give us a statement!
数十人死了 这是否你心目中的改善生活
Dozens are dead. Is this your idea of a better life?
- 这是不是一个实验  - 他疯的 这件事怎么发生的
- Was this an experiment of some kind?  - He was crazy. How did it happen?
- 你们是否制造它来控制大局  - 你对这次灾难有何感想
- Did you build it to take control?  - How do you account for this disaster?
OCP可会给受害者们赔偿
Will OCP make reparations to the victims?
那混蛋竟然可以脱身
That son of a bitch is getting away with it.
我们碰不了他
We can't even touch him.
忍耐一点吧
Patience, Lewis.
我们都不过是人罢了
We're only human.
《机械战警2》